Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Apple Computer, Inc. Records
1977-1998
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Apple Computer, Inc.
M1007
600 Linear Feet
Collection contains organizational charts, annual reports, company directories, internal communications, engineering reports, design materials, press releases, manuals, public relations materials, human resource information, videotapes, audiotapes, software, hardware, and corporate memorabilia. Also includes information regarding the Board of Directors and their decisions.
ca. 600 linear ft.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. As per legal agreement, copies of audio-visual material are only available in the Special Collections reading room unless explicit written permission from the copyright holder is obtained. The Hardware Series is unavailable until processed. For further details please contact Stanford Special Collections (specialcollections@stanford.edu).
Acquisition Information
Gift of Apple Computer, Inc., 1997.
Historical Note
Apple Computer, Inc. was incorporated on January 3, 1977. Apple Computer, Inc., ignited the personal computer revolution in the 1970s with the Apple II, and reinvented the personal computer in the 1980s with the Macintosh, of which it had sold more 30 million systems as of the end of 1998. Apple's original mission as articulated by its co-founder Steven Jobs was to bring the best personal computing products and support to students, educators, designers, scientists, engineers, business persons and consumers in over 140 countries around the world. In 1998, Apple Computer, Inc. maintained Research & Development sites in Cork, Ireland; Cupertino, California; Tokyo, Japan; and Zhuhai, China. Apple owned manufacturing facilities in the United States, Ireland, and Singapore. Distribution facilities are located in the United States, Europe, Canada, Australia, Singapore, and Japan.
Missing Title
1976 Steve Job and Steve Wozniak create the Apple computer, which is just a circuit board and does not come with a case, keyboard, mouse or monitor. Venture capitalist "Mike" Markkula invests $91,000 in the new company.
1977 The Apple II released. First personal computer with a plastic case and color graphics.
1978 Storage peripheral on Apple II changed from cassette to disk drive.
1979 Apple II+ released.
1980 Apple III released. Apple has several thousand employees, no domestic unions and goes public at $22/share.
1981 Problems with Apple III lead the company to temporarily halt production. Forty employees are laid off. Wozniak and girlfriend injured in a plane crash. Jobs becomes chairman, "Apple Values" drafted. IBM releases its first PC.
1983 Apple III+, Apple IIe and Lisa released. Lisa was the first graphical-interface computer available to the public. Lisa also comes with a mouse and a 3.5 inch disk drive. John Sculley leaves PepsiCola to run Apple. Over 200 Apple employees have become millionaires since 1980. Apple is the youngest company to enter the Fortune 500.
1984 Apple IIc, Lisa 2 and Macintosh are released. The classic "1984" commercial runs during the Superbowl.
1985 Lisa and Apple III discontinued. Lisa 2 re-released as Mac XL. Jobs resigns, Apple lays off 1200 employees and begins to look into Microsoft's GUI development after the release of Windows 1.01.
1986 Apple IIgs, enhanced Apple IIc and MacPlus released. Apple achieves Fortune 200 classification.
1987 Mac SE and Mac II released. Hypercard added to operating system.
1988 Apple IIc+ and Mac IIx released. Apple has over 9000 employees worldwide and is doing business in 85 countries. Jobs' new project NeXT is released.
1989 Mac SE/30, Mac IIcx, Mac portable and Mac IIci released. Excess Lisa computers buried in a Utah landfill.
1990 Mac IIfx, Mac Classic, Mac LC and Mac IIsi released. IBM released Windows 3.0.
1991 Classic II (later sold as Performa 200), Quadra 700, Quadra 900 and PowerBook 170 released.
1992 Mac IIvx (Performa 600 and 600CD), Mac IIvi, Quadra 950 and PowerBook 160 released.
1993 Color Classic, Color Classic II, LC III, LC III+, LC 475/ Quadra 605, LC 520, Quadra 610, Quadra 650, Quadra 800, Workgroup Server 80, PowerBook 165, PowerBook 5300 and Newton released. Scully leaves and Michael Spindler becomes CEO of Apple. NeXT computers are discontinued.
1994 LC 550, Quadra 630, PowerMac 6100 and various Performas released.
1995 Various PowerMacs, various Performas and Duo 2300c released. Apple has $1 billion in backorders. Windows 95 released.
1996 Various PowerMacs and Performas released. Spindler resigns and Gil Amelio becomes chairman. Apple buys NeXT and Jobs returns to work at Apple.
1997 Various PowerMacs and PowerBooks released. Amelio resigns. Jobs becomes "interim" CEO and crafts an alliance with Microsoft. Newton cancelled.
1998 iMac released. Apple begins to be profitable again.
Scope and Content
Contains organizational charts, annual reports, company directories, internal communications, engineering reports, design materials, press releases, manuals, public relations materials, human resource information, videotapes, audiotapes, software, hardware, and corporate memorabilia. Also includes information regarding the Board of Directors and their decisions.
Macintosh SE (Computer); Apple IIGS (Computer); Apple IIe (Computer); Corporate culture.; Macintosh Classic (Computer); Lisa computer.; Apple II (Computer); Macintosh II (Computer); Computer software industry; Macintosh (Computer); Apple III (Computer); Computer engineering; Macintosh PowerBook notebook computers.; Computers.; Computer industry.; Apple computer -- Programming.; Apple II Plus (Computer); Apple IIc (Computer); Wozniak, Steve, 1950-; Apple Computer, Inc.; Sculley, John; Apple Computer, Inc.; Apple Computer, Inc. Macintosh Division; Amelio, Gil.; Markkula, A.C. (Mike)
- Administration & Organization, Series 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes organization charts (both company-wide and for smaller divisions), telephone directories, annual reports, corporate histories and timelines.
  - Timelines & Corporate History, Subseries 1.1
    - Software & hardware release & availability dates, var. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photocopies of checks written to purchase an Apple I, 1976, July (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Ricketts, Charles
    - Corporate Timeline, 1976-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Timeline, 1976-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Timeline, 1976-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Timeline, 1976-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Timeline, 1976-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Historical pricing list, 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Revenues bargraph, 1977-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Apple products: dates introduced & discontinued, 1978-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Apple Values statement, 1981? (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Apple Corporate Library Timeline, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Apple Commemorative Calendar, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Case study of Apple Computer, Inc. for Stanford University School of Business, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Tylka, Suzanne; Gable, James S.; Stanford University
    - Introduction dates for Apple products, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Innovation at Apple, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Dvorak, John C.
    - At the Crossroads: a strategic framework for a renewed Apple, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Amelio, Gil.
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: ENIAC computer, 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: ENIAC computer, 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: ENIAC computer information plaque, text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Battle for market share informational plaque, 1950-1959; text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Byte magazine cover, Issue no. 3, 1975 Nov.; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Byte Computer Store, 1975; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Byte Computer Store information plaque, 1975; text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer original partners, circa 1975; text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple I interpreter, circa 1975; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple I interpreter informational plaque, circa 1975; text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple I schematic informational plaque, circa 1975; text mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Assembly line in garage, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Assembly line in garage, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Assembly line in garage informational plaque, 1976; text mounted on press board (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Original Apple logo, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple-I operation manual cover, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple-I operation manual cover, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple's first advertisement, 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Regis McKenna, Inc. advertising memo re: Apple Computer, 1976 June 22; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Regis McKenna, information plaque, 1976; text mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple-with-a-bite logo, circa 1976; 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple-with-a-bite logo, circa 1976; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Key strategies, 1976 Nov. 18; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Product information catalog cover, 1977 Mar.; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Patent registration no. 1078312, 1977 Nov. 29; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II: system description. In Byte Publication, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication: introducing Apple II .... Advertisement, circa 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer booth, West Coast Computer Faire, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer booth, West Coast Computer Faire informational plaque, 1977; text mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II plus, circa 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: A is for Apple: advertisement, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Scientific American advertisement featuring Steve Jobs, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer Common stock, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: AppleSoft reference manual, 1977; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Michael Scott, Apple President information plaque, 1977 - 1980; text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II reference manual, 1977 Jan.; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Continental Illinois Corp. check, 1978 Aug. 25; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Introducing Apple II: advertisement, 1978; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Writer text editing system, circa 1978; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple ad introducing Disk II floppy drives, 1978; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Bank Street writer / Broderbund Software, circa 1978; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Writer 1.1 text processing system, 1979; 1 photograph mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II advertisements, 1979; 2 photographs mounted on press board + text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II advertisements, 1979; 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple advertising information plaque, circa 1979; text mounted on press board (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Printed circuit board, [197-]; 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Printed circuit board informational plaque, [197-]; text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Whom the Apples fell on, [197-]; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Serial interface card, [197-]; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple IIs information plaque, [197-?]; text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II basic manual, ca. 1980 & Apple Pascal, 1979, 1980, 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Pascal information plaque, 1980; text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Ground-breaking ceremony, 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Ground-breaking ceremony information plaque, text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Department spotlight: Quality control, In ?: an employee newsletter, 1979 Nov.; 1 photograph of article mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Software sells systems: poster, 1979; 1 photograph of poster mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: A personal guide to personal computers, [ca. 1979]; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Dick Cavett commercial, [197-]; 6 photographs + text mounted on press board (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple bulletin: Morgan Stanley and Hambrecht and Quist offer 4,600,000 shares of Apple ...., [1980 Dec. 12]; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Stock offering information plaque, [1980 Dec. 12]; text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Softape software ad, 1980; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: The electronic canvas / by Barbara G. Gibson, circa 1980; 1 photograph of article mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Inc. magazine cover, 1981 Oct.; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Inc. magazine article, 1981 Oct.; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: A.C. (Mike) Markkula, 1981; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Baked Apple [advertisement], 1981 + Grow corn with Apple [advertisement], 1981, 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Chiat / Day information plaque, 1981; text mounted on press board (2 copies) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: A.C. (Mike) Markkula, [ca. 1981]; text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple magazine cover depicting Burt Rutan, 1981; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple magazine article re: Burt Rutan, 1981; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Annual report, 1981; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Time magazine cover, 1982 Feb. 15; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Assembly bill no. 3194, 1982 Mar. 10; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Doonesbury cartoon depicting Apple Computer, 1982 Mar. 14; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Revenge of the nerds article. In California magazine, 1982 July; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple IIc sketches, 1982 Dec.; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II forever!, 1982; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple IIc is unveiled at San Francisco's Moscone Center, 1982; text mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II forever! event, Moscone Center, San Francisco, 1982; 1 photograph mounted on press board (cy 1) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II forever! event, Moscone Center, San Francisco, 1982; 1 photograph mounted on press board (cy 2) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: How to seek less and find more: [advertisement], 1982; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer annual report, 1982; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: How to make a worksheet play: advertisement, 1982; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: VisiCalc personal software, 1982; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Magazine cover, Vol. 2, no. 2, depicting Apple III, 1982; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Fortune 500 cover, 1982; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: "Machine of the Year", Time Magazine cover, 1983 Jan. 3; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Fortune magazine cover, 1983 Feb. 7; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple makes Fortune. In Wall Street Journal, 1983 Apr. 21; 1 photograph of clipping mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: BusinessWeek magazine covers, 1983 Aug. & 1983 Oct.; 2 photographs + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: We couldn't have done it without them: [advertisement], 1983; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: John Sculley quote regarding competition, 1983; text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Del Yocam, executive vice president, [ca. 1983]; 1 photograph + text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: The man, the wheel, and the Apple: advertisement, n.d., &, The renaissance man is alive and well: [advertisement], 1983; 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: John Sculley, Apple President, 1983-, text mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: BusinessWeek cover depicting Steve Jobs and John Sculley, 1984 Nov. 26; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple credit card, 1983; 1 photograph + 1 l. text mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: We designed the new Apple IIe ....: [advertisement], 1983; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple Computer annual report, 1983; 1 photograph + 1 l. text mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: It's the same old Apple II: [advertisement], 1983; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Kid's can't wait, [ca. 1983]; 1 photograph + 1 l. text mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple III owner's guide, [ca. 1983]; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: IBM vs. Apple, PC Magazine, Vol. 3, no. 3, 1984 Feb.; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple II .... forever?, 1984; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: 1984 commercial, 5 photographs mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Chiat/Day 1984 commercial information plaque, 1 l. text mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Apple announces a breakthrough: [advertisement], 1984, &, No wonder we did so well in school: [advertisement], 2 photographs mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Annual report, 1984; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: A little competition for the Apple IIe: [Apple IIc advertisement], 1984; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Steve Wozniak and Steve Jobs at the Apple IIc introduction, [ca. 1984]; text mounted on press board (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Steve Jobs receiving check for $21 million from Morgan Stanley, 1985 [i.e. 1978] Dec. 22; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Apple timeline exhibit, 1945 - 1985: Microsoft Word for Macintosh advertisement, [ca. 1985]; 1 photograph mounted on press board (Box 17, Folder 3)